<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="campfire1_text">You are on a camping trip with your
        family and are looking for an area to set up your campfire.
        You see four possible locations to dig your fire pit. Which
        of the following locations do you choose?</string>
    <string name="campfire2_text">As you are sitting around the fire
        with your five year old brother and parents, you need to go
        to the restroom. You go to the bathroom with:</string>
    <string name="campfire3_text">Your family starts to roast
        marshmallows, but your marshmallow catches on fire! What do
        you do?</string>
    <string name="campfire4_text">It\'s getting late, and your family
    decides to call it a day. What do you do?</string>
    <string name="campfire5_text">You know that your campfire has been
        fully extinguished and it is safe to leave when:</string>

    <string name="campfire1a">under a tree with low branches</string>
    <string name="campfire1b">in an open area</string>
    <string name="campfire1c">in a windy area</string>
    <string name="campfire2a">your brother</string>
    <string name="campfire2b">your parents</string>
    <string name="campfire2c">your entire family</string>
    <string name="campfire3a">blow out the fire</string>
    <string name="campfire3b">wave the marshmallow around until the flame dies</string>
    <string name="campfire3c">throw the marshmallow away as far as possible</string>
    <string name="campfire4a">try to blow out the fire with all your might</string>
    <string name="campfire4b">just leave it there, it will eventually go out on its own</string>
    <string name="campfire4c">pour lots of water on the fire</string>
    <string name="campfire5a">You\'ve poured your entire bucket of water on the fire.</string>
    <string name="campfire5b">The leftover coal and ash is cold to the touch, and you don\'t see any more embers.</string>
    <string name="campfire5c">There are still a few embers exposed, but they\'ll all go out eventually.</string>

    <string name="cf_toast1a">Oh no! One of the tree branches catches on fire. Try again.</string>
    <string name="cf_toast1b">Great idea! There\'s nothing around you that can catch on fire.</string>
    <string name="cf_toast1c">Uh oh! The wind blows the fire towards a nearby bush, and it catches on fire. Try again.</string>
    <string name="cf_toast2a">Good job! This means that there are still adults attending the fire.</string>
    <string name="cf_toast2b">Uh oh. The only person left at the fire is your little brother.
        There should always be an adult at the fire. Try again.</string>
    <string name="cf_toast2c">Now everybody has left the fire, but there should always be an adult attending it. Try again.</string>
    <string name="cf_toast3a">Good job! You safely blew out your burning marshmallow.</string>
    <string name="cf_toast3b">Oh no! The marshmallow hits your brother as you\'re waving it around
        and he gets burned. Try again.</string>
    <string name="cf_toast3c">Oh no! Your burning marshmallow lands in a bush, which catches on fire. Try again.</string>
    <string name="cf_toast4a">You won\'t be able to extinguish your fire like this. Try again.</string>
    <string name="cf_toast4b">You cannot be sure that the fire goes out. After you leave,
        it spreads to a bush, which catches on fire. Try again.</string>
    <string name="cf_toast4c">Great idea! Pouring water on the fire will make it go out.</string>
    <string name="cf_toast5a">Even though you\'ve poured the entire bucket, there could still be leftover
        embers, which may not go out on their own. Try again.</string>
    <string name="cf_toast5b">Good job! Your fire has been completely extinguished, and it is safe to leave.</string>
    <string name = "cf_toast5c">Uh oh! The fire doesn\'t go out, and there is a gust of wind that blows it towards
        a bush, which catches on fire. Try again.</string>
</resources>